<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Python Sul 2025 - Porto Alegre</title><link>https://pysul.python.com.br/en/</link><description>Recent content on Python Sul 2025 - Porto Alegre</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 03:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pysul.python.com.br/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Python Sul's Code of Conduct</title><link>https://pysul.python.com.br/en/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pysul.python.com.br/en/code-of-conduct/</guid><description>&lt;p>The &lt;strong>Python Sul&lt;/strong> conference is a friendly, inclusive, and harassment-free environment where everyone is welcome and where civility is compulsory.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Conference organizers offer a &lt;strong>Response Team&lt;/strong> acting in order to guarantee such an environment.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="therefore">Therefore:&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>We will not tolerate harassment, inappropriate discrimination, or public humiliation of any kind.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>We will not tolerate non-compliance with Brazilian laws.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Regardless of their role, every person taking part in the conference is subject to these rules.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="thus-we-understand">Thus we understand:&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Harassment&lt;/strong> is the act of insisting, persecuting, or coercing someone into involuntary behavior.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Inappropriate discrimination&lt;/strong> is the act of pulling apart, insulting, or humiliating someone by promoting their exclusion based on any particular attribute.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Public humiliation&lt;/strong> is the act of subjugating, pulling down, ridiculing, or publicly promoting the vexation of others.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="target-audience-and-suitability">Target audience and suitability&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The target audience of the conference also includes children and adolescents; thus we stand for a suitable environment for all age groups. In that sense, &lt;strong>language and sexualized images&lt;/strong> are not suitable for lectures and promotional actions by sponsors.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>